I know who you are.
You know me?
You are the daughter of Lu Jingcheng and Yu Wen.
You got it wrong.
Lu Jingcheng is my father,
but my mother
is Annie.
You and the boy from the Lu family
are half-siblings.
Annie isn't your biological mother.
Back then,
the Lu and An families
were joined by marriage for profit.
Before they got married,
both of them
had their own lovers.
This marriage
was just a show
from the beginning.
After getting married,
they lived their own lives.
[Coincidentally,]
[they both had children with their lovers]
[around the same time,]
[and their due dates were close.]
[Unfortunately,]
[your birth mother died]
[from amniotic fluid embolism]
[during childbirth.]
[Shortly after,]
[your father]
[was diagnosed with advanced lung cancer.]
Before he died,
he left you 30% of the company's shares
and put them in trust.
When you have a child,
the shares will be transferred back to your name in batches.
And he entrusted you to me.
Not long after your father died,
Annie found you.
But that woman was too cunning.
She closed the orphanage.
I could only watch you be taken away by her.
I was powerless.
She was afraid that I would tell the truth,
so she forced me to disappear forever.
I went to a foreign country.
You're lying.
What evidence do you have?
You have a plum birthmark on your waist,
which is exactly the same as your mother's.
Five years ago,
a girl named Su Muchen
took all your adoption papers from me.
Didn't she show you?
Is what she said true?
Building 6, Family Compound 23, Chemical Fiber Factory.
It's Su Muchen's studio.
The documents of the Sunlight Welfare House
were taken by Su Muchen
from Dean Li.
Su Muchen is still alive.
No way.
Who is Purple Vine?
Annie adopted me
because of the 30% shares I inherited.
My shares have already been diluted by 15%.
If all my shares are diluted,
how can I survive
in the Lu family with nothing?
Who?
Who's there?
Ah!
Jiang Li!
Bats!
There are bats in the living room.
I hit it with a book
just now.
It's okay.
The payment is 31.8 yuan.
It should have hurt its wing.
I didn't expect you to be afraid of such a small thing.
In the dark,
who can tell if it's a parrot or a bat?
But why are you in front of my house?
Because I live next door.
When did you move here?
I live in 1801.
I should have moved in
earlier than you.
500 yuan,
12 days.
You knew I lived here.
It's really special for you
to know your neighbors.
Stop it.
I...
I just knew it.
You're really not good at lying.
But what are we going to do
with it later?
You can only wait until it recovers
and then release it.
No, no, no.
I can't keep pets.
You hurt it with a book.
Whether it's fate
or a debt,
you have to take responsibility.
Why don't you keep it?
I...
I'll be moving into the Lu family's house in a few days.
I don't have time to take care of it.
Fine.
Then give it a name.
I'm not very good at this.
You do it.
Then I'll call it Momo.
You're Young Master Shen,
and it's Momo.
You two make a good roommate.
Okay.
It's my treat today.
You're moving into the Lu family?
Yeah.
That's how you win over a playboy's heart,
and avoid being dumped.
Are you really going to marry a scum like Lu Xu?
Or what?
At least he's young,
not some old guy who can't even walk.
You have plenty of choices.
Why choose this?
I know the path I've taken,
and I know where the future lies.
I'm not a princess,
and I don't expect a prince charming.
So,
I won't expect a gentleman
like you.
How do you know if you don't try?
Don't joke with me.
I'm not joking.
Come on.
The food is getting cold.
Are you leaving again after this?
Or what?
Today is my birthday.
Happy birthday.
That's it?
What else?
I hope you can give me a gift.
Only today,
I hope you can
not treat me as a substitute for her,
and love me once.
If you are not a substitute,
you are nothing.
Honey, you're back.
Are you tired today?
When did you come back?
I just got back today.
Hey.
I can do it myself.
What?
I haven't been back for a few days.
I just missed you.
Do you miss me?
Of course.
I made you bird's nest porridge.
I'll bring it to you.
Honey,
did something happen
in Singapore?
No.
What's wrong?
Just asking.
I met a friend
in Singapore.
He said something
I think
he's right.
Love is not always passionate.
It's a lamp in the night,
a glass of water in the morning.
We've carried the bitterness of life together,
and tasted the sweetness of life together.
As long as we hold hands,
we can keep going.
Although we are husband and wife,
we are also each other's
most trusted comrades
and eternal destination.
In the past,
you have endured a lot of my whims,
and silently contributed a lot to this family.
But after the wedding, I realized
I should be a virtuous wife
and a good mother.
I will be your harbor.
From now on,
as long as we hold hands,
we'll keep moving forward,
right?
You should get some rest.
I'll bring the bird's nest soup
to the bedroom.
Okay.
Honey, hurry up...
Li,
you finally moved into the old house.
You came back from Singapore so soon.
I was worried about you,
so I came back early.
I brought you a gift.
What a beautiful dress.
It's like tailor-made for me.
Go prepare the tea and snacks.
How did it go?
Don't worry.
It's all taken care of.
Those women
will have no ties with brother-in-law.
I trust you.
You can do it.
Try it on.
Okay.
So many Tiff accessories.
You seem to like this brand.
Because it never caters to fashion trends,
but pursues simple and elegant lines
and timeless beauty.
Clive Kristin perfume.
You like this perfume, too?
Yes.
Because even if it's the same model and the same perfume,
it will be adjusted to a different scent
according to different people.
The point is
it will never be the same as others.
What's the scent of yours?
Clive Kristin.
No.1.
Mine is not the same
from the others.
It has a hint of bitterness
and despair.
How is it?
Does it look good?
Perfect.
It's simply
tailor-made for you.